American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File 5001 PAM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 1, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: The Industrial Commission of Ohio and Wallace D. Yaple, H. B. Hammond and P.J. Daily, Comprising the Industrial Commission of Ohio, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Commonwealth v Boston & Maine R.R., 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: The People of the State of New York vs. C. Klinok Packing Company, Appellate, 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Court of Appeals, 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Author: Frederick H. Cunningham
- Box: 1, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: State of North Dakota, ex rel, Henry Amerland, Relator vs. John H. Hagan, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Radtke Brothers, et al., Appellants vs. Industrial Commission of Wisconsin and Herbert Rutzinske Respondents, 1921; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: State of North Dakota ex rel. Henry Amerland, Relator, Plaintiffs, vs. John W. Hagan. Et al. Dependants and Dependents, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Olindo and Philo Francischiello, Castlinglione, Messer, Province of Chieti, Italy vs. Pennsylvania Coal Co., Defendants, Scranton, PA., 1922; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: The Industrial Commission of Ohio, Et Al., vs. David Brown, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: Charles Johnson, against Hedden Construction Company, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Author: Edward J. Redington
  - Item 7: In the matter of the application of the railroads entering Topeka to close freight stations situated in said city at four o'clock p.m. on each week day except Saturday, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Brief in Opposition, 1923; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Author: Jeremiah F. Connor
  - Item 9: Capital Traction Co. v. Hoff, 174 U.S. 4, 40., 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: James Wiley Epperson vs. William Howell, Gus Carlson, and Mans H. Coffin, as the Board ofCounty Commissioners of Ada County, Idaho., 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: Old Age Pension, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: G.P. Jones vs. P.J. McBride, Genevieve Chalkley and John Craddock, constituting the Industrial Welfare Commission of the State of Kansas, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: State of Wisconsin, vs. Lange Canning Company, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Box: 1, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Louis Paonessa Compensation, 1925; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Clara W. B. Busser, Aubrey H. Weightman, Carl A. Ziegler, Edward F. Beale, Benjamin H. Ludlow, and The F.H. White Company, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Clara W. B. Busser, et al., vs. Charles A. Snyder, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Workmen's Compensation Opinions, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Donald C. Swearingen et al. Vs. John C. Bond, Auditor, etc., 1925; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: The State of North Dakota, vs. Ed HER, Manager of Waverly Caf, 1927; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Louis Schumer, against Harry Caplin, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Bethelem Shipbuilding Corporation, Ltd., vs. A. Kostreken, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: Cora M. Deranleau vs. James Furling, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Emma Arola et al., vs The Pacific Lumber Company, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: Dr. S. H. Hunkin vs. H. N. Gray, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 12: 11433 Acker vs. Miller Creamery and New Amesterdam Quality Company, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 13: #11046, Johnson vs. Western Pacific Railroad Company, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 14: Globe Indemnity Company Petitioner, vs. Industrial Accident Commission. And Ernest Kopp, Respondents., 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 15: Rupert Ribnik vs. Andrew F. McBride, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Box: 2, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: International and Great Northern Railroad Company, plaintiff in error, v. United States of America, Defendant in Error, No. 1776. International & Great Northern Railroad Company, Plaintiff in error, 1900; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Lizzie Alida Sexton vs. The Newark District Telegraph Company, 1911; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: William P. Martin
  - Item 3: St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company of Texas, Plaintiff in Error vs. The united States of America, Defendant in Error, 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Wabash Railroad Company, Plaintiff in Error, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The United States of America, Plaintiff in Error, vs. Colorado and Northwestern Railroad Company, Defendant in Error, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The United States of America, Plaintiff in Error, vs. Coloradio & North Western Railroad Company, Defendant in Error, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Pacific Coast Railway Company, A Corporation, Plaintiff in Error, vs. United States of America, Defendant in Error, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Pacific Coast Railway Company, A Corporation, Plaintiff in Error vs. United States of America, Defendant in Error, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company, Plaintiff in Error vs. United States of America, Defendant in Error, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Grace Watson, Administratrix vs. St. Louis, Iron Mountain & Southern Railway Company, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: United States of America, Plaintiff in Error, vs. Illinois Central Railroad Company, Defendant in Error, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: No. 1938 Gulf, Colorado & Santa Fe Railway Company, plaintiff in error vs. United States of America, Defendant in Error, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Mayer Ziegler vs. Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Chicago Junction Railway Company, Plaintiff in Error, vs. William R. King, Defendant in Error, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Chicago & Northwestern Railway Company, Plaintiff in Error, vs. United States of America, Defendant in Error, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Union Stock Yards Company, of Omaha, Plaintiff in Error vs. United States, Defendant in Error, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Chicago, Burlignton & Quincy Railway Company, Plaintiff in Error, vs. United States of America, Defendant in Error, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Wabash Railroad Company, Plaintiff in Error, vs. United states of America, Defendant in Error, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Belt Railway Company of Chicago, Plaintiff in Error vs. United States of America, Defendant in Error, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: United States v. Atchinson, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Donegan v. Baltimore & New York Railway Company, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Chicago, Milwaukee & St. Paul Railway Company v. United States, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Box: 2, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The People of the State of New York against Charles Schweinler Press, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Box: 2, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Galveston, Harrisburg & San Antonio Railway Company, Plaintiff in Error v. United States of America, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Trinity and Brazos Valley Railway Company vs. United States of America, 1903; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: St. Louis & San Francisco Railroad Company, Plaintiff in error, vs. E. M. Delk, Defendant in Error, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Box: 2, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Charles Schlemmer vs. The Buffalo, Rochester and Pittsburgh Railway Company, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: E.M. Delk Petitioner and Defendant in Error vs. St. Louis and San Francisco Railroad Company, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: G.W. Wathen vs. Jackson Oil & Refining Company, et al., 1912; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Mayer Ziegler, Petitioner, against Pennsylvania Railroad Company, Respondent, 1908; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Curt Muller, Plaintiff in Error vs. State of Oregon, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Anna Hawley vs. Joseph Walker, Constable, Etc., 1913; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: El Paso & Northeastern Railway Company, Plaintiff in Error, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Pacific States Telephone and Telegraph Company, Plaintiff in Error vs. The State of Oregon, 1911; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Box: 2, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Bridget McGovern, Administratrix of the Estate of Peter McGovern, Deceased, Plaintiff in Error, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: T.B. Cottage, Plaintiff in Erro, vs. The State of Kansas, 1915; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Bridget McGovern, Administratic of the Estate of Peter McGovern, Deceased, Plaintiff in Error vs. Philadelphia & Reading Railway Company, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: William B. Bosley, Peter L. Wheeler, and Samuel H. Buteau, Trustees of "The Samuel Merritt Hospital," and Ethel E. Nelson, Appellants vs. John P. McLaughlin, Labor Commissioner of the State of California et al., 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: F.A. Miller, Plaintiff in Error, vs. F.P. Wilson, Sheriff of the County of Riverside, State of California, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: William Truax, Sr., Wiley E. Jones, Attorney General of the State of Arizona, and W.G. Gillmore, County Attorney of Cochise County, Arizona, Appellants, 1915; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: William E. Heim, cranford Company, and Flinn-O 'Rourke Company, Inc., Plaintiffs in Error vs. Edward E. McCall, Milo R. Maltbie, J. Sargeant Cram, George V.S. Williams and Robert C. Wood as Members of and Constitutiing the Public Service Commission for th, 1915; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Clarence A. Crane, Plaintiff in Error, vs. The People of the State of New York, 1915; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Psinr Lumber Company et al vs. Elbridge H. Neal individally and as Secretary and Treasurer of the Joint District Council of New York and Vicinity of the Brotherhood of Carpenters etc., et al, 1917; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: F.A. Miller vs F.P. Wilson/ William B. Bosley, et al., vs. John P. McLaughlin, Labor Commissioner of the State of California, et al., William B. Bosley, et al., vs. John P. McLaughlin, Labor Commissioner of the State of California, et al., 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Joe Adams et al. Appellants, vs. W.V. Tanner, Attorney General of the State of Washington, and George H. Crandell, Prosecuting Attorney of Spokane County, State of Washington, 1916; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: United States Supreme Court Advance Opinions, 1916; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: 36 U.S. Supreme Court Reporter 482 Texas Texas & Pacific Railray Company. Vs. Rigsby, 1916; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Box: 2, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Madera Sugar Pine Company, (a Corporation) vs. Industrial Accident Commission of the State of California, and Geronima Venegas, by Jos. Barcloft (her attorney in fact), 1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Madera Sugar Pine Company a corporation, vs. Industrial Accident Commission of the State of California and Geronima Venegas., 1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Madera Sugar Pine Company, Plaintiff in Error vs. Industrial Accident Commission of the State of California and Geronima Vengeas, by Jos. Barcroft, her attorney in fact./ Madera Sugar Pine Company, Plaintiff in Error, vs. Industrial Accident Commission of, 1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Knickerbocker Ice Company, Plaintiff in Error vs. Lillian E. Stewart, 1919; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Frank C. Thornton and the Cleveland Stamping and Tool Company, Plaintiffs in Error, vs. Thomas J. Duffy and Herbert L. Eliot, members of and composing the Industrial Commission of Ohio, 1920; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Quong Ham Wah Company, Plaintiff in Error, vs. Industrial Accident Commission of the State of California et al., 1920; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Western Fuel Company, Petitioner, vs. Antone Garcia, as Administrator of the Estate of Manuel Souza, Deceased, 1921; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: The State Industrial Commission of the State of New York Petitioner, vs. Nordenholt Corporation and the Travelr's Insurance Company, 1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: No. Original Commonwealth of Massachusetts Plaintiff, vs. Andrew W. Mellon, Secretary of the Treasury, et Als. Defendants, 1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Box: 2, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Industrial Accident Commission of the State of California and Josep Hayes, Thomas Hayes, Helen Hayes and Mary Hayes, Minors, By Mary Lordan, Guardian of their Persons and Estates vs. James Rolph Company and general Accident, Fire and Life Assurance Corpor, 1923; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: R.E. Sheehan Company and Aetna Life Insurance Company, Plaintiffs in Error, vs. George K. shuler, as State Treasurer of the State of New York; John D. Higgins, Richard H. Curran, and Francis Perkins, as and Constituting the State Industrial Board of the S, 1923; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Jospeh Radice, Plaintiff in Error, vs. People of the State of New York, 1924; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: New York State Railways, Plaintiff in Error, vs. George K. Shuler, as Treasurer of the State of New York; John D. Huggins, Richard H. Curram, et al.,&c, 1924; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: R.E. Sheehan Company and Aetna Life Insurance Company, Plaintiffs in Error, vs. George K. Shuler, as State Treasurer of the State of New York; John D. Higgins, Richard H. Curran, and Francis Perkins, as and constituting the State Industrial Board of the S, 1923; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Panama Railroad Company, against, Andrew Johnson, 1923; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Rubert Ribnik, against, Andrew F. McBride, 1927; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Dahlstrom Metallic Door Company and Jamestown Mutual Insurance Company, vs. Industrial Board of the State of New York and Paul Helfrick, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Sam Michaelson, Dan Cullen, Fred Henstra, et al., Petitioners, vs. The United States, ex rel. Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis & Omaha Railway Company, 1924; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Pasquale Liberato and Anna Capon Liberato, by their Attorney in fact, Giovanni Disanto, Plaintiff in error vs. S.A. Royer and Albert Herr, doing business as Royer & Herr, et al., 1926; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Box: 2, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Workers and National defense, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Emory Olson Appointment Announced by Administrator McNutt, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Engineering Colleges Announce Defense Training Courses, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Defense Planning and Labor Policy, 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Plan, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Schedule Annual Meeting American Engineering Council of Federated American Engineering Societies, 1924; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Plan of Amalgamation of the Council of Organizations with the Community Councils of National Defense, 1919; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Frederick L. Cranford
- Box: 2, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Occupational Specifications and Classification as a Basis for the Operation of Public Employment Exchanges, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Report of the Commission on Economy and Efficiency to the Governor of the State of Maryland Concerning The Consolidation of State Offices having to do with Labor Conditions, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Econometrica; Journal of the Econometric Society, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Is There Enough to Go 'Round? The National Income as Seen by Bureau of Economic Research, 1919; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Albert deSilver
  - Item 5: Hunger Stalks Through West Virginia, 1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Lawrence Dwyer
  - Item 6: The Coming of Industry to the South, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: T.D.A. Cockerell
  - Item 7: A National Industrial Inventory, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Sixth Annual Industrial Conference of the State of New York Buffalo, 1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Some Observations on Workers' Organizations, 1928; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Morris Llewllyn Cooke
  - Item 10: National Conference on Economic Society, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Preliminary Announcement of the Twenty-Third Annual Meeting of the American Economic Association, 1910; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Box: 2, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Social Economic Efficiency, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: Sven Svantesson
  - Item 2: Long Range Planning for the Regulation of Industry, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: J.M. Clark
  - Item 3: Ten Facts on Technology and Employment, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Convention P., 1920; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: On the Tendency of Labor Saving to Increase Compensation Costs, 1925; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: Leslie L. Hall
  - Item 6: Fatigue Study, 1920; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: Frank B. Gilbreth
  - Item 7: How Scientific Management can Promote a New Functional Status for Workers, 1928; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: Geoffrey C. Brown
  - Item 8: Workers participation in creativecProduction Twenty-five selected cases., 1921-1928 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Social Economic Efficiency Part 2, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: A Reconstruction Program, 1920; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: H. F. J. Porter
- Box: 2, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Report of the Commission to Investigate Employment Offices, 1911; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Alliance Employment Bureau, 1913; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Labour Exchanges, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Author: W. H. Beveridge
  - Item 4: Laws governing Free Employment Offices and Private Employment Agencies in Illinois as Amended and in force on and from July 1, 1909, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Laws Governing Free Employment Offices and Private Employment Agencies in Illinois as amended and in force on and from July 1, 1913, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Chapter 227 Laws 1918 an Act to Regulate the Keeping of Empoyment Agencies, 1913; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Bulletin of the Industrial Commission of Wisconsin, 1913; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Labor Exchanges Act, 1909., Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: General Regulations made by the Board of Trade in Pursuance of Section (2) of the Labour Exchanges Act, 1909, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Statuory Rules and Orders, 1910, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Box: 2, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Sub Committee of Standing Employment Bureau Auxiliary Committee and Resolution, 1915; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Tentative Proposals for Consideration on the Question of Public and Private Employment Offices, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Public Employment Exchanges, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Vocational Guidance and the Work of The Vocation Bureau of Boston, 1915; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Public Employment Exchanges, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Constitution and By-Laws of the Metropolitan Association of Employment Agents of Greater New York City, 1917; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Tentative Proposals for Consideration on the Question of Public and Private Employment Offices, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Constitution, 1915; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: The Boston Placement Bureau Report, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Record of the Vocation Bureau of Boston, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Boston Free Employment Office, 1914; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Laws Governing Free Employment Offices and Private Employment Agencies in Illinois as amended and in force on and from July 1, 1915, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Organized Non-Commercial Employment Work for Juveniles in New York City, 1916; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: To His Royal Highness the Governor General in Council, 1915; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Box: 2, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Hearings Before the Committee on Ways and Means House of Representatives with Reference to The New Revenue Bill, 1918; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Report of the Committee of Inquiry into the Work of the Employment Exchanges, 1920; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Statutory Rules and Orders No. 601 Labour Exchanges, 1917; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Employment Agency Law, 1917; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Authorized to Organize State Free Employment Bureau, 1917; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Free Employment Bureau, 1917; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Employment Department; Employment Exchanges, 1917; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Employment Agency Law, 1917; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: To the Editor, 1919; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Author: Frank G. Patchin
  - Item 10: Private Employment Agencies of Illinois, 1919; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Author: John J. McKenna
  - Item 11: Chapter 227 Laws 1918 An Act to Regulate the Meeting of Employment Agencies, 1917; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: International Association of Public Employment Services Ninth Annual Meeting, 1921; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Annual Report of the Director General U.S. Employment Service To the Secretary of Labor, 1920; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Report of the Committee of Inquiry into the Work of the Employment Exchanges, 1920; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Box: 2, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: What Industry Expects From A Public Employment Office, 1925; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The Employment Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Bureau of Personnel Administration, 1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Manual for Conducting "Service at Cost" Community Placement Bureaus with A Plan for Nationalization, 1926; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Author: Hans C. Pfund
  - Item 5: Public Works Conference Organizations and Official Delegates and Minutes, 1924; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Author: P. N. Moore